<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<language>
	<page id="33232474" title="DeadAir Script T Files" descr="names used in DeadAir Scripts" voice="no">
		<!-- DONE: Library entries like job names etc -->
		<!-- DONE: hover descriptions for dynamic war -->
		<t id="100">DA Mod Menu</t>
		<!-- Submod Menus 101-109 -->
		<t id="101">DA Dynamic War</t>
		<t id="102">DA Dynamic News</t>
		<t id="103">DA Evolution</t>
		<t id="104">DA Fill</t>
		<t id="105">DA Jobs</t>
		<t id="106">DA Gate</t>
		<t id="107">DA God</t>
		<t id="108">DA Blueprint Analysis</t>
		<t id="109">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- Dynamic War Menu Entries -->
		<t id="110">Increase Relations</t>
		<t id="111">Decrease Relations</t>
		<t id="112">Recent News</t>
		<t id="113">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="114">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="115">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="116">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="117">(Options Menu){1001,2600}</t>
		<t id="118">Unlock Relations</t>
		<t id="119">DW Ignored Factions</t>
		<t id="120">Insufficient Relation</t>
		<t id="121">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="122">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="123">Enable Dynamic War</t>
		<t id="124">Enable DW Favors</t>
		<t id="125">Dynamic War Interval</t>
		<t id="126">Close Ally Weight</t>
		<t id="127">Large Increase Weight</t>
		<t id="128">Small Increase Weight</t>
		<t id="129">Small Decrease Weight</t>
		<t id="130">Large Decrease Weight</t>
		<t id="131">Nemesis Weight</t>
		<t id="132">No Change Weight</t>
		<t id="133">Primary Race Modifier</t>
		<t id="134">Current Relations Modifier</t>
		<t id="135">Common Relations Modifier</t>
		<t id="136">Enable DW Flavor Text</t>
		<t id="137">Enable DW Debug</t>
		<t id="138">Locked</t>
		<t id="139">Unlocked</t>
		<t id="140">Allowed</t>
		<t id="141">Ignored</t>
		<t id="142">Enable AI Relations Cap</t>
		<t id="143">Maximum Factions to Check</t>
		<t id="144">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="145">Sector Faction Logic Menu</t>
		<!-- Dynamic War Menu Entry Descriptions -->
		<t id="1110">Allows the player to use credits or favors to increase relations between two factions.</t>
		<t id="1111">Allows the player to use credits or favors to increase relations between two factions. Decreasing relation between two factions requires a certain level of trust (reputation) with the faction.</t>
		<t id="1112">Shows recent events similar to logbook.</t>
		<t id="1113">Shows the amount of military ships that each supported faction has.</t>
		<t id="1114">Shows the amount of economic ships and stations that each supported faction has.</t>
		<t id="1115">Shows a general overview of a faction's amount of wares stored compared to amount desired.</t>
		<t id="1116">Shows a general overview of a faction's station storage split between stations that produce a ware and stations that consume a ware.</t>
		<t id="1117">Collection of options available to change how the Dynamic War script runs.</t>
		<t id="1118">Allows the player to unlock a factions relation. This may cause issues with certain storyline missions.</t>
		<t id="1119">Allows the player to enable or disable certain factions from Dynamic War script. Disabling a faction may help avoid issues with certain storyline missions.</t>
		<t id="1120">You do not have enough reputation with (FACTION)</t>
		<t id="1121">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1122">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1123">Changes whether the Dynamic War script will continue to run. Disabling does not revert relations.</t>
		<t id="1124">Changes whether the player will continue to accrue favors for maintaining 20+ relation with a faction.</t>
		<t id="1125">Changes the time \(in minutes\) between Dynamic War events. Default = 30 minutes</t>
		<t id="1126">Changes the weighting of events where two factions' relation will increase TO 25. To calculate percent chance, take this weight and divide by total weight of events. Default = 1</t>
		<t id="1127">Changes the weighting of events where two factions' relation will increase BY 15. To calculate percent chance, take this weight and divide by total weight of events. Default = 16</t>
		<t id="1128">Changes the weighting of events where two factions' relation will increase BY 5. To calculate percent chance, take this weight and divide by total weight of events. Default = 32</t>
		<t id="1129">Changes the weighting of events where two factions' relation will decrease BY 5. To calculate percent chance, take this weight and divide by total weight of events. Default = 32</t>
		<t id="1130">Changes the weighting of events where two factions' relation will decrease BY 15. To calculate percent chance, take this weight and divide by total weight of events. Default = 16</t>
		<t id="1131">Changes the weighting of events where two factions' relation will decrease TO -30. To calculate percent chance, take this weight and divide by total weight of events. Default = 1</t>
		<t id="1132">Changes the weighting of events where two factions' relation will NOT change. To calculate percent chance, take this weight and divide by total weight of events. Default = 0</t>
		<t id="1133">Changes the effect that a factions primary race plays. Factions will tend to be more friendly with same race and xenophobic the higher this value is. This value is multiplicative. Default = 0.25</t>
		<t id="1134">Changes the effect that a factions current relation plays. Factions will tend to continue friendly relations or continue hostility the higher this value is. This value is multiplicative. Default = 0.5</t>
		<t id="1135">Changes the effect that a factions current allies and enemies plays. Factions will tend to form coalitions the higher this value is. This value is multiplicative. Default = 0.25</t>
		<t id="1136">TODO. Changes whether logbook entries have added flavor text. Does not affect gameplay but takes a lot of work to write them.</t>
		<t id="1137">Changes whether debug entries in the code will output text or files. Has no effect if game is not run in the appropriate debug mode.</t>
		<t id="1138">This faction has locked relations.</t>
		<t id="1139">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1140">This faction is able to be selected in the Dynamic War script. Only factions that are active, claim space, and have unlocked relations will be chosen.</t>
		<t id="1141">This faction will not be selected by the Dynamic War script.</t>
		<t id="1142">Changes whether a script that limits and corrects faction relations will run. This script prevents AI to AI relations above 27 to avoid meeting the "Self" condition. It also corrects {20203,701} relations to match {20203,601} to avoid civil war.</t>
		<t id="1143">The number of factions the script will have as potential second faction during an event. Increasing this value can potentially cause an impact to performance as there is a large amount of calculations for determining faction strength. Default = 4</t>
		<t id="1144">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1145">Allows the player to change whether faction logic in Clusters and their child Sectors is enabled. This menu will force the cluster and child sectors to be on the same setting if changed to avoid problems with AI. This may cause issues with certain storyline missions.</t>
		<!-- Dynamic War Misc -->
		<t id="2110">(FACTION)Relations Locked.</t>
		<t id="2111">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2112">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2113">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2114">Relation too high.</t>
		<t id="2115">Diplomatic Favor</t>
		<t id="2116">Cluster</t>
		<t id="2117">Change in count compared to %s minutes ago.</t>
		<t id="2118">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2119">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2120">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2121">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2122">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2123">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2124">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2125">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2126">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2127">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2128">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2129">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- Evolution Menu Entries -->
		<t id="160">Enable Evolution</t>
		<t id="161">Evolution Interval</t>
		<t id="162">Evolution Current Level / Max Level</t>
		<t id="163">Enable Evolution Xenon Fleets</t>
		<t id="164">Maximum Xenon Fleets Added</t>
		<t id="165">Xenon Fleet Size</t>
		<t id="166">Small Fleet</t>
		<t id="167">Medium Fleet</t>
		<t id="168">Large Fleet</t>
		<t id="169">Enable Evolution Debug</t>
		<t id="170">Enable Xenon Station Evolution</t>
		<t id="171">Enable Evolution Fast Fleet Ordering</t>
		<t id="172">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="173">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="174">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="175">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="176">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="177">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="178">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="179">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- Evolution Menu Entry Descriptions -->
		<t id="1160">Changes whether the Evolution script will continue to run. Disabling does not revert ships already upgraded.</t>
		<t id="1161">Changes the time \(in minutes\) between evolution level increases. Has no effect if Evolution disabled or already at max level. Default = 120 minutes</t>
		<t id="1162">Shows the current progress level of Evolution.</t>
		<t id="1163">Changes whether additional ships are built by xenon.</t>
		<t id="1164">Changes the maximum number of Xenon fleets that will be ordered built by Xenon from this mod. Default = 10 fleets</t>
		<t id="1165">Size of the Xenon fleets added by Evolution. This will only affect future fleets built. Default = Medium</t>
		<t id="1166">1{1001,48}(XL) - 1{1001,48}(XL) {1001,7817}(Escort) - 3{1001,50}(M) {1001,7817}(Escort) - 6{1001,51}(S) {1001,7817}(Escort)</t>
		<t id="1167">1{1001,48}(XL) - 3{1001,48}(XL) {1001,7817}(Escort) - 9{1001,50}(M) {1001,7817}(Escort) - 18{1001,51}(S) {1001,7817}(Escort)</t>
		<t id="1168">1{1001,48}(XL) - 5{1001,48}(XL) {1001,7817}(Escort) - 15{1001,50}(M) {1001,7817}(Escort) - 30{1001,51}(S) {1001,7817}(Escort)</t>
		<t id="1169">Changes whether debug entries in the code will output text or files. Has no effect if game is not run in the appropriate debug mode.</t>
		<t id="1170">Changes whether Xenon shipyards and wharves will expand at evolution levels 1,3, and 5. At each of these tiers shipyards will add two additional storage modules, an additional XL ship builder, and an additional defense module. Wharves will add one additional storage module and one energy cell module.</t>
		<t id="1171">Changes whether Xenon will order one or multiple Evolution fleets at a time. If enabled, Xenon will order one fleet at each shipyard. If disabled, Xenon will order one fleet at one shipyard. Fleets ordered will respect Maximum Xenon Fleets Added amount.</t>
		<t id="1172">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1173">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1174">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1175">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1176">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1177">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1178">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1179">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- Evolution Misc -->
		<t id="2160">Branch 9 Evolution {1001,1112}</t>
		<t id="2161">Branch 9 Evolution {1001,7817}</t>
		<t id="2162">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2163">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2164">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2165">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2166">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2167">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2168">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2169">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2170">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2171">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2172">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2173">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2174">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2175">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2176">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2177">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2178">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2179">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- Fill Menu Entries -->
		<t id="200">Enable Fill</t>
		<t id="201">Fill Interval</t>
		<t id="202">Max {20102,1051} Ware %</t>
		<t id="203">Adjusted Max {20102,1051} Ware %</t>
		<t id="204">Min {20102,1051} Ware %</t>
		<t id="205">Adjusted Min {20102,1051} Ware %</t>
		<t id="206">Min {20102,1071}/{20102,1081} Ware %</t>
		<t id="207">Adjusted Min {20102,1071}/{20102,1081} Ware %</t>
		<t id="208">Enable Fill Ship Mods</t>
		<t id="209">Enable Fill Debug</t>
		<t id="210">Enable Fill Fleet Ship Mods</t>
		<t id="211">Enable Fill Ship Paint Mods</t>
		<t id="212">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="213">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="214">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="215">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="216">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="217">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="218">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="219">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- Fill Menu Entry Descriptions -->
		<t id="1200">Changes whether the Fill script will continue to run.</t>
		<t id="1201">How often Fill will check stations. Default=60</t>
		<t id="1202">The lowest percentage of capacity a ware can be before removing cargo at the {20102,1051}. Set to 100 to disable the removal of cargo. Default=90.</t>
		<t id="1203">The percentage capacity a ware will be after removing cargo at the {20102,1051}. Default=75.</t>
		<t id="1204">The highest percentage of capacity a ware can be before adding cargo at the {20102,1051}. Set to 0 to disable the adding of cargo. Default=5.</t>
		<t id="1205">The percentage capacity a ware will be after adding cargo at the {20102,1051}. Default=10.</t>
		<t id="1206">The highest percentage capacity a ware can be before adding cargo at the {20102,1071}/{20102,1081}. Set to 0 to disable the adding of cargo. Default=5.</t>
		<t id="1207">The percentage capacity a ware will be after adding cargo at the {20102,1071}/{20102,1081}. Default=10.</t>
		<t id="1208">Changes whether the Fill script will add ship mods to a random XL/L ship of the station owner when resources are drained.</t>
		<t id="1209">Changes whether debug entries in the code will output text or files. Has no effect if game is not run in the appropriate debug mode.</t>
		<t id="1210">Changes whether the Fill script will add ship mods to all subordinates of the selected Military ship.</t>
		<t id="1211">Changes whether the Fill script will paint ships that have mods added to them.</t>
		<t id="1212">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1213">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1214">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1215">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1216">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1217">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1218">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1219">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- Fill Misc -->
		<t id="2200">Added</t>
		<t id="2201">Removed</t>
		<t id="2202">Modified</t>
		<t id="2203">Net</t>
		<t id="2204">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2205">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2206">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2207">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2208">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2209">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2210">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2211">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2212">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2213">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2214">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2215">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2216">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2217">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2218">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2219">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- Jobs Menu Entries -->
		<t id="240">Enable Expeditions</t>
		<t id="241">Enable Smart Sector Tags</t>
		<t id="242">Enable Jobs Exped Debug</t>
		<t id="243">Enable Jobs SST Debug</t>
		<t id="244">Enable Jobs SST Extra Debug</t>
		<t id="245">Jobs Quotas</t>
		<t id="246">Critical {1001,11284}(Sector) {1004,24}(Patrol)</t>
		<t id="247">Core {1001,11284}(Sector) {1004,24}(Patrol)</t>
		<t id="248">Border {1001,11284}(Sector) {1004,24}(Patrol)</t>
		<t id="249">Contested {1001,11284}(Sector) {1004,24}(Patrol)</t>
		<t id="250">Small Fleet</t>
		<t id="251">Medium Fleet</t>
		<t id="252">Large Fleet</t>
		<t id="253">Galaxy Quota</t>
		<t id="254">Sector Quota</t>
		<t id="255">{1001,49}(L) {1002,12032}(Trader)</t>
		<t id="256">{1001,50}(M) {1002,12032}(Trader)</t>
		<t id="257">{1001,49}(L) {20204,5601}(Mineral Miner)</t>
		<t id="258">{1001,50}(M) {20204,5601}(Mineral Miner)</t>
		<t id="259">{1001,49}(L) {20204,5701}(Gas Miner)</t>
		<t id="260">{1001,50}(M) {20204,5701}(Gas Miner)</t>
		<t id="261">Vanilla Spawned Jobs Menu</t>
		<t id="262">Job ID</t>
		<t id="263">Remove Space Job Exclusivity</t>
		<t id="264">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="265">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="266">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="267">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="268">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="269">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- Jobs Menu Entry Descriptions -->
		<t id="1240">Changes whether the added expeditions jobs for factions will continue to be built, organized, and launched to attack enemies.</t>
		<t id="1241">Changes whether the custom logic for determining Critical, Core, Border, and Contested sector jobs will continue to be built, organized, and launched to reinforce sectors.</t>
		<t id="1242">Changes whether debug entries in the code will output text or files. Has no effect if game is not run in the appropriate debug mode.</t>
		<t id="1243">Changes whether debug entries in the code will output text or files. Has no effect if game is not run in the appropriate debug mode.</t>
		<t id="1244">Changes whether debug entries in the code will output text or files. Has no effect if game is not run in the appropriate debug mode. These debugs are extremely detailed and extensive.</t>
		<t id="1245">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1246">This job patrols sectors that are considered critical to a faction. The sectors must include a shipyard or wharf AND be owned by the faction.</t>
		<t id="1247">This job patrols sectors that are considered to be the core sectors. The sectors must not border enemy sectors or be contested. Sector must be owned by the faction and typically contains economic stations not expected to be under considerable threat.</t>
		<t id="1248">This job patrols sectors that border enemy or unfriendly sectors. The sectors must be owned by the faction and are expected to be under considerable threat.</t>
		<t id="1249">This job patrols sectors that have enemy or unfriendly presence in the sector. The sector must include at least one station owned by this faction and an enemy faction. These sectors are considered under considerable threat and the faction will attempt to increase it's control.</t>
		<t id="1250">%s(#) {1002,12061}(Capital Ship) + %s(#) {1002,12061}(Capital Ship) {1001,7817}(Escort) + %s(#) {1001,50}(M) {1001,7817}(Escort) + %s(#) {1001,51}(S) {1001,7817}(Escort)</t>
		<t id="1251">%s(#) {1002,12061}(Capital Ship) + %s(#) {1002,12061}(Capital Ship) {1001,7817}(Escort) + %s(#) {1001,50}(M) {1001,7817}(Escort) + %s(#) {1001,51}(S) {1001,7817}(Escort)</t>
		<t id="1252">%s(#) {1002,12061}(Capital Ship) + %s(#) {1002,12061}(Capital Ship) {1001,7817}(Escort) + %s(#) {1001,50}(M) {1001,7817}(Escort) + %s(#) {1001,51}(S) {1001,7817}(Escort)</t>
		<t id="1253">This number is the number of fleets the faction will attempt to maintain across the entire galaxy. If this number is set to 0 it will disable future orders of these fleets.</t>
		<t id="1254">This number is the maximum number of fleets the faction will attempt to maintain in each sector that meets the criteria. If this number is set to 0 it will disable future orders of these fleets.</t>
		<t id="1255">This job trades an assorted collection of container goods using a large sized ship.</t>
		<t id="1256">This job trades an assorted collection of container goods using a medium sized ship.</t>
		<t id="1257">This job mines assorted minerals using a large sized ship.</t>
		<t id="1258">This job mines assorted minerals using a medium sized ship.</t>
		<t id="1259">This job mines assorted gasses using a large sized ship.</t>
		<t id="1260">This job mines assorted gasses using a medium sized ship.</t>
		<t id="1261">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1262">This is the internal name of the job that spawns these ships under unmodified circumstances. There is no way to tell if the job has been changed to be built via scripting.</t>
		<t id="1263">This option when toggled will remove the exlusive attribute from sectors that have been set-up to only allow jobs added by that extension. This is primarily used in the Boron DLC to prevent other jobs. When disabled, settings will be reset to default.</t>
		<!-- Jobs Misc -->
		<t id="2240">Strategic Patrol</t>
		<t id="2241">Interior Patrol</t>
		<t id="2242">Boundary Patrol</t>
		<t id="2243">Arbitrator Patrol</t>
		<t id="2244">(Destroyer Escort){20221,4001} {1001,7817}</t>
		<t id="2245">(Frigate Escort){20221,3011} {1001,7817}</t>
		<t id="2246">(Fighter Escort){20204,2601}</t>
		<t id="2247">Fleet Size</t>
		<t id="2248">{33232474,245} menu available once {33232474,241} is set to true.</t>
		<t id="2249">Could not find appropriate faction jobs, check for poorly written diffs to jobs.xml.</t>
		<t id="2250">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2251">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2252">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2253">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2254">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2255">{20109,101}(Container) {20221,4011}(Freighter)</t>
		<t id="2256">{20109,101}(Container) {20221,3031}(Transporter)</t>
		<t id="2257">{1001,49}(L) {20204,5601}(Mineral Miner)</t>
		<t id="2258">{1001,50}(M) {20204,5601}(Mineral Miner)</t>
		<t id="2259">{1001,49}(L) {20204,5701}(Gas Miner)</t>
		<t id="2260">{1001,50}(M) {20204,5701}(Gas Miner)</t>
		<t id="2261">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2262">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- News Menu Entries -->
		<t id="280">Enable Dynamic News</t>
		<t id="281">Enable DN Notifications</t>
		<t id="282">Enable DN Logbook</t>
		<t id="283">Enable DN News Storage</t>
		<t id="284">DN Interval</t>
		<t id="285">Enable DN Debug</t>
		<t id="286">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="287">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="288">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="289">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="290">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="291">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="292">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="293">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="294">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="295">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="296">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="297">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="298">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="299">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- News Menu Entry Descriptions -->
		<t id="1280">Changes whether the Dynamic News script will continue to run.</t>
		<t id="1281">Changes whether Dynamic News will send notifications on monitored events.</t>
		<t id="1282">Changes whether Dynamic News will write to the logbook on monitored events.</t>
		<t id="1283">Changes whether Dynamic News will store recent news events.</t>
		<t id="1284">Changes the minimum time between the script checking for any new reports. This will change the time between checks for groups of reports that will be output in regular intervals.</t>
		<t id="1285">Changes whether debug entries in the code will output text or files. Has no effect if game is not run in the appropriate debug mode.</t>
		<t id="1286">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1287">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1288">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1289">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1290">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1291">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1292">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1293">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1294">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1295">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1296">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1297">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1298">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1299">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- News Misc -->
		<!-- $FACTION$ extending station $STATION_NAME$ ($STATION_IDCODE$) in $SECTOR_NAME$ -->
		<t id="2280">%1 extending station %2 \(%3\) in %4.</t>
		<!-- $FACTION$ extending station $STATION_NAME$ ($STATION_IDCODE$) with $MODULE_NAME$ in $SECTOR_NAME$ -->
		<t id="2281">%1 extending station %2 \(%3\) with additional %4 in %5.</t>
		<!-- $FACTION$ extending station $STATION_NAME$ ($STATION_IDCODE$) with $NUMBER$ modules in $SECTOR_NAME$ -->
		<t id="2282">%1 extending station %2 \(%3\) with additional %4 modules in %5.</t>
		<!-- $FACTION$ building new $WARE$ station in $SECTOR_NAME$ -->
		<t id="2283">%1 building new %2 station in %3.</t>
		<!-- $STATION$ in $SECTOR$ destroyed -->
		<t id="2284">%s in %s destroyed</t>
		<!-- by $KILLER$ -->
		<t id="2285">by %s</t>
		<!-- Stations lost: -->
		<t id="2286">Stations lost:</t>
		<!-- $STATION$ in $SECTOR$ -->
		<t id="2287">%s in %s</t>
		<!-- Expanded $STATION$($IDCODE$) in $SECTOR$ -->
		<t id="2288">Expanded %s\(%s\) in %s</t>
		<!-- with $NUMBER$ modules -->
		<t id="2289">with %s modules</t>
		<!-- Stations expanded: -->
		<t id="2290">Stations expanded:</t>
		<!-- Started $STATION$($IDCODE$) in $SECTOR$ -->
		<t id="2291">Started %s\(%s\) in %s</t>
		<!-- to produce $WARE$ -->
		<t id="2292">to produce %s</t>
		<!-- New stations started: -->
		<t id="2293">New stations started:</t>
		<!-- $NUMBER$ stations destroyed -->
		<t id="2294">%s stations lost</t>
		<!-- $NUMBER$ stations expanded -->
		<t id="2295">%s stations expanded</t>
		<!-- $NUMBER$ stations started -->
		<t id="2296">%s stations started</t>
		<t id="2297">{33232474,112} menu available once {33232474,280} and {33232474,283} are set to true.</t>
		<t id="2298">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2299">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- Gate Menu Entries -->
		<t id="300">Enable DA Gate</t>
		<t id="301">Enable Gate Debug</t>
		<t id="302">Show All Gates</t>
		<t id="303">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="304">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="305">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="306">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="307">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="308">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="309">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="310">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="311">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="312">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="313">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="314">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="315">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="316">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="317">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="318">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="319">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- Gate Menu Entry Descriptions -->
		<t id="1300">Changes whether the DA Gate script will continue to run. This only affects the scripts that find the gates, it does not revert gate status.</t>
		<t id="1301">Changes whether debug entries in the code will output text or files. Has no effect if game is not run in the appropriate debug mode.</t>
		<t id="1302">Changes whether the DA Gate script will show all gates in this menu or just predefined gates from list.</t>
		<t id="1303">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1304">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1305">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1306">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1307">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1308">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1309">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1310">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1311">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1312">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1313">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1314">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1315">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1316">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1317">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1318">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1319">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- Gate Misc -->
		<t id="2300">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2301">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2302">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2303">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2304">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2305">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2306">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2307">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2308">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2309">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2310">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2311">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2312">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2313">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2314">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2315">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2316">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2317">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2318">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2319">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- God Menu Entries -->
		<t id="340">Enable DA God</t>
		<t id="341">Enable God Debug</t>
		<t id="342">Show Quota Settings</t>
		<t id="343">Production Ware</t>
		<t id="344">Additional Modules to Build</t>
		<t id="345">Activate DA God for %s</t>
		<t id="346">Already Activated</t>
		<t id="347">Enable God Extra Debug</t>
		<t id="348">(Options Menu){1001,2600}</t>
		<t id="349">God Quotas</t>
		<t id="350">Allow Build in Player Owned Sector</t>
		<t id="351">Attempt Recovery</t>
		<t id="352">Allow Build in Friendly Owned Sector</t>
		<t id="353">Enable Ship Building Station Upgrades</t>
		<t id="354">Station Build Interval Multiplier</t>
		<t id="355">Station Max Module Setting</t>
		<t id="356">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="357">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="358">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="359">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- God Menu Entry Descriptions -->
		<t id="1340">Changes whether the DA God options are available in the menu. This does not run the script or change anything in the game on it's own.</t>
		<t id="1341">Changes whether debug entries in the code will output text or files. Has no effect if game is not run in the appropriate debug mode.</t>
		<t id="1342">Displays the quota settings for this faction. No settings are applied until the Activate DA God for Faction button has been selected.</t>
		<t id="1343">The ware produced by the station ordered by the DA God script.</t>
		<t id="1344">The number of modules that will be built by the DA God script. Stations will each have up to 25 modules each when requested. Each ware and increment of 25 would result in an additional station so be aware that this may affect performance. The default values are calculated from several hundred hours of accumulated data for a strong and balanced economy.</t>
		<t id="1345">This will trigger the script to run for this faction when this button is clicked. It will use the numbers set above on the sliders and is not reversible. The faction will attempt to maintain the number of modules set not including vanilla module count.</t>
		<t id="1346">The script for this faction has already been activated. Multiple runs for the same faction is not yet supported.</t>
		<t id="1347">Changes whether debug entries in the code will output text or files. Has no effect if game is not run in the appropriate debug mode. These debugs are extremely detailed and extensive.</t>
		<t id="1348">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1349">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1350">Changes whether the DA God script can order stations in a player owned sector if the faction has no sectors and has at least 20 relation with player. This does not alter normal vanilla station ordering behaviour.</t>
		<t id="1351">Changes whether the DA God script will attempt to reorder/rebuild destroyed or failed stations that contain production modules from this mod. This does not attempt to rebuild modules not added by this mod.</t>
		<t id="1352">Changes whether the DA God script can order stations in friendly owned sector if the faction has no sectors and has at least 20 relation with faction. This does not alter normal vanilla station ordering behaviour.</t>
		<t id="1353">Changes whether the DA God script can order upgrades for a shipyard or wharf. Each station will only be upgraded once but the script will continue to check for new stations.</t>
		<t id="1354">Adjusts the time between ordering stations for each faction. This is a multiplier to the coded time min max values. Default time between ordering stations is 20-25 minutes for initial stations and 25-30 minutes for recovery. Increasing this value will slow down the build up of stations.</t>
		<t id="1355">Adjusts the amount of modules that the script will attempt to place on a single station.</t>
		<t id="1356">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1357">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1358">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1359">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- God Misc -->
		<t id="2340">Production Ware</t>
		<t id="2341">Additional Modules to Build</t>
		<t id="2342">{33232474,349} menu available once {33232474,340} is set to true.</t>
		<t id="2343">Warning: Did not detect a mod that increases plot size and prevents reduction. This may cause issues with station generation due to space constraints. Recommend using a value at or below 10.</t>
		<t id="2344">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2345">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2346">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2347">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2348">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2349">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2350">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2351">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2352">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2353">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2354">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2355">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2356">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2357">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2358">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2359">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- BP Menu Entries -->
		<t id="380">(Options Menu){1001,2600}</t>
		<t id="381">(Progress Menus){1001,9513} {1001,4836}</t>
		<t id="382">(Station Modules){1001,9610}</t>
		<t id="383">(Ships){1001,6}</t>
		<t id="384">(Equipment){1001,7935}</t>
		<t id="385">Enable DA Blueprint Analysis</t>
		<t id="386">Adjust Scan Requirements</t>
		<t id="387">Enable BP Debug</t>
		<t id="388">(Misc){1001,2664}</t>
		<t id="389">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="390">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="391">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="392">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="393">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="394">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="395">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="396">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="397">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="398">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="399">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- BP Menu Entry Descriptions -->
		<t id="1380">This is a category for object classes not coded into the mod that are scanned.</t>
		<t id="1381">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1382">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1383">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1384">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1385">Changes whether the Blueprint Analysis script will capture ship and station scans to award progress for unlocking blueprints.</t>
		<t id="1386">Changes the number of scans for a class of objects required to unlock the blueprint. Change takes effect on the next scan of an object.</t>
		<t id="1387">Changes whether debug entries in the code will output text or files. Has no effect if game is not run in the appropriate debug mode.</t>
		<t id="1388">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1389">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1390">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1391">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1392">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1393">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1394">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1395">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1396">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1397">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1398">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1399">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- BP Misc -->
		<t id="2380">(Unknown Object Class){1001,9002} {1001,9197}</t>
		<t id="2381">The original mod that inspired this was made by Jack the Stripper and permission to continue the mod was granted.</t>
		<t id="2382">(XS Ships){1001,52} {1001,6}</t>
		<t id="2383">(S Ships){1001,51} {1001,6}</t>
		<t id="2384">(M Ships){1001,50} {1001,6}</t>
		<t id="2385">(L Ships){1001,49} {1001,6}</t>
		<t id="2386">(XL Ships){1001,48} {1001,6}</t>
		<t id="2387">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2388">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2389">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2390">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2391">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2392">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2393">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2394">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2395">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2396">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2397">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2398">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2399">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- Info Menu Entries -->
		<t id="400">DA Information Menus</t>
		<t id="401">Military Ship Count</t>
		<t id="402">Economic Ship/Station Count</t>
		<t id="403">(Ware Stored/Wanted){1001,45} {1001,1406}\/{1001,2903}</t>
		<t id="404">Station Storage</t>
		<t id="405">Production Module Count</t>
		<t id="406">Trader Profit Menu</t>
		<t id="407">Enable DA Trader Profit Tracking</t>
		<t id="408">Ship Details Menu</t>
		<t id="409">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="410">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="411">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="412">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="413">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="414">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="415">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="416">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="417">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="418">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="419">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- Info Menu Entry Descriptions -->
		<t id="1400">Information Menus</t>
		<t id="1401">Shows the amount of military ships that each supported faction has.</t>
		<t id="1402">Shows the amount of economic ships and stations that each supported faction has.</t>
		<t id="1403">Shows a general overview of a faction's amount of wares stored compared to amount desired.</t>
		<t id="1404">Shows a general overview of a faction's station storage split between stations that produce a ware and stations that consume a ware.</t>
		<t id="1405">Shows a general overview of a faction's amount of production modules.</t>
		<t id="1406">Shows a general overview of DeadTater and TaterTrader profits.</t>
		<t id="1407">Changes whether the Trader Profit script will continue to track player owned traders. Disabling this option will reset tracked data.</t>
		<t id="1408">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1409">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1410">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1411">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1412">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1413">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1414">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1415">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1416">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1417">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1418">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="1419">(XXX)</t>
		<!-- Info Menu Misc -->
		<t id="2400">Change in count compared to %s ago.</t>
		<t id="2401">Blue = Stored</t>
		<t id="2402">Green = Excess</t>
		<t id="2403">Red = Shortage</t>
		<t id="2404">Producer</t>
		<t id="2405">Consumer</t>
		<t id="2406">Total lifetime estimated profit</t>
		<t id="2407">Lifetime estimated profits are not completely accurate due to the effects of discounts and commissions at this time.</t>
		<t id="2408">Estimated profit per hour</t>
		<t id="2409">Hourly estimated profit is based on start time of the default behaviour for the ship and does not account for interruptions.</t>
		<t id="2410">Number of ships</t>
		<t id="2411">Change in number of ships since last viewed</t>
		<t id="2412">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2413">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2414">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2415">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2416">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2417">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2418">(XXX)</t>
		<t id="2419">(XXX)</t>
	</page>
</language>
